maximindia.in 2018-10-08

# Maxim India - Privacy Policy

                                 Maxim India - Privacy Policy
1. Introduction
1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; in this policy we
explain how we will treat your personal information.
1.2 [We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this
policy when you first visit our website.] OR [By using our website and agreeing to this
policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.]
2. Collecting personal information
2.1 We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:
(a) [information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website
(including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating
system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths])];
(b) [information that you provide to us when registering with our website (including [your
email address])];
(c) [information that you provide when completing your profile on our website (including
[your name, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies,
educational details and employment details])];
(d) [information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email
notifications and/or newsletters (including [your name and email address])];
(e) [information that you provide to us when using the services on our website, or that is
generated in the course of the use of those services (including [the timing, frequency and
pattern of service use])];
(f) [information relating to any purchases you make of our [goods] OR [services] OR [goods
and/or services] or any other transactions that you enter into through our website (including
[your name, address, telephone number, email address and card details])];
(g) [information that you post to our website for publication on the internet (including [your
user name, your profile pictures and the content of your posts])];
(h) [information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or send
through our website (including [the communication content and metadata associated with the
communication])]; and
(i) [any other personal information that you choose to send to us].
2.2 Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain
that person's consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in
accordance with this policy.

3. Using personal information
3.1 Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes
specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website.
3.2 We may use your personal information to:
(a) [administer our website and business];
(b) [personalise our website for you];
(c) [enable your use of the services available on our website];
(d) [send you goods purchased through our website];
(e) [supply to your services purchased through our website];
(f) [send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from
you];
(g) [send you non-marketing commercial communications];
(h) [send you email notifications that you have specifically requested];
(i) [send you our email newsletter, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if
you no longer require the newsletter)];
(j) [send you marketing communications relating to our business [or the businesses of
carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you, by post or, where
you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any
time if you no longer require marketing communications)];
(k) [provide third parties with statistical information about our users (but those third parties
will not be able to identify any individual user from that information)];
(l) [deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to our website];
(m) [keep our website secure and prevent fraud]; and
(n) [verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of our website
[(including monitoring private messages sent through our website private messaging
service)]].
3.3 If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and
otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.
3.4 Your privacy settings can be used to limit the publication of your information on our
website, and can be adjusted using privacy controls on the website.

3.5 We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third
party for the purpose of their or any other third party's direct marketing.
4. Disclosing personal information
4.1 We may disclose your personal information to [any of our employees, officers, insurers,
professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for
the purposes set out in this policy.
4.2 We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies
(this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as
reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.
4.3 We may disclose your personal information:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information
to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
(d) [to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are
contemplating) selling]; and
(e) [to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent
authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such
court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal
information].
4.4 Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third
parties.
5. International data transfers
5.1 Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any
of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in
accordance with this policy.
5.2 Personal information that you publish on our website or submit for publication on our
website may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or
misuse of such information by others.
5.3 You expressly agree to the transfers of personal information described in this Section 5.
6. Retaining personal information
6.1 This Section 7 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to
help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion
of personal information.

6.2 Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for
longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
6.3 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 6, we will retain documents
(including electronic documents) containing personal data:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal
proceedings; and
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information
to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).
7. Security of personal information
7.1 We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss,
misuse or alteration of your personal information.
7.2 We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and
firewall-protected) servers.
7.3 All electronic financial transactions entered into through our website will be protected by
encryption technology.
7.4 You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently
insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
7.5 You are responsible for keeping the password you use for accessing our website
confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to our website).
8. Amendments
8.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.
8.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this
policy.
8.3 We may notify you of changes to this policy [by email or through the private messaging
system on our website].
9. Your rights
9.1 You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you;
provision of such information will be subject to:
(a) the payment of a fee; and

(b) the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity [(for this purpose, we will usually
accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor)].
9.2 We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.
9.3 You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing
purposes.
9.4 In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal
information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of
the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.
10. Third party websites
10.1 Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites.
10.2 We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices
of third parties.
11. Updating information
11.1 Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be
corrected or updated.
12. Cookies
12.1 Our website uses cookies.
12.2 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by
a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to
the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
12.3 Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will
be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by
the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of
the user session, when the web browser is closed.
12.4 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but
personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and
obtained from cookies.
12.5 We use both session and persistent cookies on our website.
12.6 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies; for example:
(a) in Internet Explorer (version 11) you can block cookies using the cookie handling
override settings available by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy" and then
"Advanced";

(b) in Firefox (version 44) you can block all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options",
"Privacy", selecting "Use custom settings for history" from the dropdown menu, and
unticking "Accept cookies from sites"; and
(c) in Chrome (version 48), you can block all cookies by accessing the "Customise and
control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Content settings", and
then selecting "Block sites from setting any data" under the "Cookies" heading.
12.7 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
12.8 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.
12.9 You can delete cookies already stored on your computer; for example:
(a) in Internet Explorer (version 11), you must manually delete cookie files (you can find
instructions for doing so at http://windows.microsoft.com/engb/internet-explorer/delete-
manage-cookies#ie=ie-11);
(b) in Firefox (version 44), you can delete cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options" and
"Privacy", then selecting "Use custom settings for history" from the drop-down menu,
clicking "Show Cookies", and then clicking "Remove All Cookies"; and
(c) in Chrome (version 48), you can delete all cookies by accessing the "Customise and
control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Clear browsing data",
and then selecting "Cookies and other site and plug-in data" before clicking "Clear browsing
data".
12.10 Deleting cookies will have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.
13. Our details
13.1 This website is owned and operated by Burda Media India Pvt. Ltd.
13.2 Our registered office is New Delhi.
13.3 Our principal place of business is at Gurgaon.
14.4 You can contact us:
(a) [by post, using the postal address given in Contact Us];
(b) [using the website contact form on www.maximindia.in];
(c) [by telephone, on [the contact number published on our website from time to time]]; or
(d) [by email, using [the email address published on our website from time to time]].
